{
    "subject": "resource/Mya_Byrne",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/New_Jersey",
    "human_readable": "Mya Byrne is from New Jersey.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9840828776359558,
            "question": "Is Mya Byrne originally from New Jersey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8705061078071594,
            "question": "Where is Mya Byrne from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8615866303443909,
            "question": "Does Mya Byrne have any connections to New Jersey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7427076697349548,
            "question": "What is the name of the state Mya Byrne comes from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7103317975997925,
            "question": "What kind of person is Mya Byrne?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6330860257148743,
            "question": "Is New Jersey a place someone could be from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6082085371017456,
            "question": "Where might Mya Byrne live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48293033242225647,
            "question": "What information can you tell me about Mya Byrne's origins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44666728377342224,
            "question": "What state is Mya Byrne's home?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4454807937145233,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Mya Byrne?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mya Byrne is from New Jersey.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4964_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What state is Mya Byrne's home?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4964_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What information can you tell me about Mya Byrne's origins?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4964_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might Mya Byrne live?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4964_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4964_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4964_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4964_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4964_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4964_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4964_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4964_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4964_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4964_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4964_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information clearly states that \"Mya Byrne loved country music since her childhood in New Jersey,\" which supports the statement that Mya Byrne is from New Jersey."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}